that is, look, you
то есть смотрите Вы в европейскую часть
will be
России будете
pulling fuel from China to the European part of Russia,
тянуть топливо из Китая из
bringing it from China. I am not an economist, but I am
Китая привозить Я не экономист но я
considering this option. And why is
такой вариант рассматриваю А почему так
it so? Does China trade in fuel or does China itself buy fuel from others? I
покупает топливо у других А вот этого я
don’t know about this, but I think that if there is a good  price
не знаю но я думаю что если хорошую цену
can be indicated and
обозначить то можно и
bought Hello Andrey
прикупить здравствуйте Андрей
Hello Damn I can hear myself in the
Здравствуйте Блин я себя слышу в
sound Well I can hear you well Yes it's just
звук Ну я вас слышу хорошо Да просто
a little light We've already talked
немножко лёгкая Мы с вами уже общались
Yes it happened Yes I remember you visually but I
Да было дело Да я вас визуально помню но
don't remember what about either you are normal
не помню о чём или вы нормальны
or I am normal let's do it this way  we'll
или я нормальный давайте так
determine Well, now we'll find out What are you
определим Ну вот сейчас и выясним Что
discussing today about strikes on Tatarstan
обсуждаете сегодня удары по Татарстану
How did it
как так
happen technically
получилось технически
Well, there's no way for air defense to close all
Да ну нет возможности ПВО закрыть все
all territories all objects That's how it
все территории все объекты Вот так и
happened I understand that means that in
получилось понял то есть получается в
principle Ukraine will continue to bomb
принципе Украина и дальше будет бомбить
Any objects at such a long distance
На таком далёком расстоянии любые
Yes,
объекты Да
Russian  I think that such cases
российские Я думаю что такие случаи
will be repeated yes
будут повторяться да
I understand that I still think that it will be
Я так понимаю ещ у Я думаю что будет
repeated why It is
повторяться поему Это
obvious and it seems to me that I see
очевидно и мне кажется что я смотрю
the intensity is increasing
интенсивность нарастает
that not a week
что не неделя
then A well that's right B  recently
то А ну это да В последнее время
they've cleaned it up Well, you know, this is the
зачистили Ну это же знаете это вот
eternal eternal struggle between the projectile and the
извечная извечная борьба снаряда и
bro at some point
бро какой-то момент
attack, your actions are being tightened at
наступайте уплотняется свои действия в
some point there
какой-то момент с российской стороны
will be some kind of response from the Russian side to this, the
будет какая-то какой-то ответ на это
intensity
интенсивность
will decrease So it's all like that
уменьшится Так что это всё вот так
interesting interesting yes
вот интересно интересно да
yes such things are good things I like
да такие дела хорошие дела Мне нравится
such dynamics of events dynamics of events
такая динамика событий динамика событий
not
не
a big deal why Well for you not a big deal for us
шибка почему Ну для вас не шибка для нас
a big deal for you not a big deal for us a big deal but
шибка для вас не шибка для нас шибка а
What What do you like about this Well look 2
Что Что вам нравится в это Ну смотри 2
years ago Russia was shelling us and we
года назад Россия нас обстреливала а мы
Russia is not there and now the intensity of
Россию нет а теперь интенсивность
shelling of the Russian
обстрелов Российской
Federation will increase will increase will
Федерации увеличится увеличится
increase Ukraine is now bothering not
увеличится Украина достаёт теперь не
just some Belgorod but they are bothering
просто какой-то Белгород а достают
territories 1200
территории за 1200
km away and in response nothing is happening in
км а в ответ ничего не происходит в
response nothing
ответ ничего
that's what is there What was not there
вот что такое есть Что не было
before no no that's all clear Let's
раньше нет нет это всё понятно Давайте
know  M what I want to suggest
знаете М что хочу предложить Давайте
Let's try to predict How
попробуем спрогнозировать Как будут
things will progress further we can't
дальше дела продвигаться мы не можем
predict by not
спрогнозировать по не
predict
прогнози
not date
недат
about I think that Russia will grow closer to me
про Я думаю что рос ближа ме
will face a
будет Россия столкнётся с дефицитом
fuel shortage now Ukraine has already knocked out 14% according to
топлива сейчас уже Украина выбила 14% по
your data according to yours It was not me who came up with it
вашим данным по вашим Это не я придумал
It is your statistics 14% of production
Это ваша статистика 14% производственных
capacity of non-processing plants
мощностей не перерабатывающих заводов
it does not just fly into the admin
оно же прилетает не просто в админ
building it flies into the primary
здание прилетает установку первичной
processing plant this avt and that's it some
обработки вот этот авт и всё некоторые
plants There are two  installations One is knocked out
заводы Там две установки Одна выбита
works half in some knocked out
работает наполовину в некоторых выбита
two do not work at all that is this is a
две не работает вообще то есть это
fuel shortage I understood yes what will this
дефицит топливо я понял да к чему это
lead to problems with with passive with a
приведёт к проблемам с с пасивно с
passive company not only with not
пассивной компанией не только с не
just in a passive company will increase e
просто в пассивную компанию увеличится э
fuel consumption in a passive company
потребление топлива в пассивную компанию
that is e  in a passive company you will
то есть э в пассивную компанию у вас
start to have a fuel shortage At first it
начнётся дефицит топлива Сначала он
will be local if we continue to
будет локальный если мы продолжим
effectively knock out
эффективно так выбивать ещё на
your pzsh for another month it will be on a
протяжении месяца ваши пзш он будет на
huge part of the territory of Russia
огромное количество территории России
When Russia hit us on the oil depot
Когда Россия била у нас по нефтебаза
I remember it was on the oil
помню было по нефтеперерабатывающему
refinery there in Kremenchug And so on
заводу там в Кременчуге И так дальше
Ukraine  very quickly reorient
Украина очень быстро переориентировать у
our territory is small and export from
нас территория небольшая и экспорт из
abroad is so
заграницы так
driven fuel there
гоняется топливо там
Bulgaria Hot from Poland From Romania from there
Болгария Хот с Польши С Румынии оттуда
Everything is very fast for us everything
Всё у нас очень быстро всё
adapted literally a month and
адаптировалась буквально месяц и до сих
everything is still fine that is we do not depend
пор всё нормально то есть мы не зависим
on these capacities
от этих мощностей
Russia in
Россия в
case of destruction there are still 10-15 about
случае уничтожение ещё там 10-15 про
fuel generation production Where
генерации топлива производства Откуда
will such reserves be
будет такие запасы
replenished in such a territory
пополнять на такой территории
in I think fuel import So where from
во Я думаю импорт топлива Так откуда
Where from Well who do we have  neighbors China
Откуда Ну кто у нас соседи Китай
Mongolia Kazakhstan Belarus that is
Монголия Казахстан Беларусь то есть
look you
смотрите Вы европейскую часть
will
России будете
pull fuel from China from
тянуть топливо из Китая из
China bring from China I am not an economist but I am
Китая привозить Я не экономист но я
considering this option And why is it so
такой вариант рассматриваю А почему так
and China trades fuel or China itself
а Китай торгует топливом или Китай сам
buys fuel from others I don’t
покупает топливо у других вот это не
know but I think that  if you set a good price
знаю но я думаю что если хорошую цену
then you can buy it no so
обозначить то можно и прикупить нет так
if you set a good price then it is better to buy from
если хорошую цену тогда лучше купить у
the one who sells and not from China Well if
того кто продаёт а не у Китая Ну если
China itself buys
Китай сам покупает
energy resources the question of price for some
энергоресурсы вопрос цены за какую-то
price I think Chinese companies
цену Я думаю китайские компании
will agree to sell fuel not for whatever
согласятся продать топли не так за какую
you want  Venezuela may ask a question like, well
вам и Венесуэла может вопрос типа ну
then it's easier for you to bring it to
тогда проще вам его привести в Северный
some Northern port, for example, and not drive it from China
какой-то поррт например а не из Китая
by land,
гнать по земле
so the question is, now the infrastructure. Do you
так вопрос а теперь инфраструктура У вас
have the infrastructure to handle such
есть инфраструктура для прогона таких
volumes of oil? More precisely, not even oil, but
объёмов нефти Да точнее даже не нефти а
already  finished products because you have oil
уже готовой продукции потому что нефть у
Yes, look, you produce oil the
вас Да смотри нефть у вас производится
problem will be that it will not be able to
проблема будет в том что она не сможет
process Let's wait here until it's
перерабатывать Давай подождём тут до
finished and there's a month or two left Then Look, you
повно и осталось месяц-два То Смотри ты
tell me let's make a forecast I
мне говоришь давай спрогнозируйте
asked you say let's wait
запросил ты говоришь давай подождём
No, well, we are now I am now  you know I
Нет ну мы сейчас я сейчас знаешь я
just came to the conclusion that
сейчас просто пришёл к выводу что мы
now we can build whatever we want there didn't
сейчас можем какие угодно там строить не
like the
понравился
forecast Not being economists yes So
прогноз Не будучи экономистами да Так а
why are you saying then Look you said
зачем ты тогда говоришь Смотри ты сказал
let's forecast I say We are not
давай по прогнозируем Я говорю Мы ж не
forecasters well come on well come on I
прогнозисты ну давай ну давай я по
forecasted I told you I  you asked to
прогнозировал я тебе я тебе предложил
predict the further development of
спрогнозировать дальнейшее развитие
military actions is
военных действий
absolutely correct military actions That's exactly
правильно абсолютно военны Вот именно
military actions They do not occur in a vacuum
военные действия Они же не в вакууме
they rely on economics but
происходят они опираются на эконо
if you have a problem with
если у вас будет проблема с
oil products This will affect military
нефтепродуктами Это скажется на военных
actions that's what you
действиях вот как вы
think Come on, come on,
думаете Вот давай давай
predict
спрогнозируйте
That's how it is in the production of military military
Так на производстве военных военной
products  will affect will
продукции скажется
affect unlikely how
скажется вряд ли как вряд
unlikely That's how
ли Вот так
unlikely kamuto sub something from point A to exactly b
вряд камуто суб чтото с точки А в точ б
and he doesn't have  gasoline to buy
а у него нет бензина чтобы купить потому
because the line is half a day do you think it
что очередь полдня ты думаешь настолько
will be so bad Yeah I think no I think yeah
ВС будет плохо да я думаю нет я думаю да
I think it will be cooler than with
я думаю будет прикольнее чем с
eggs Come on Come on well with eggs it's
яйцами Вот давай Вот давай ну с яйцами
just such a
прям такая
tragedy we were dying of hunger from this
трагедия с голоду загибались от этой
price of eggs awful And look we are  it's
цены на яйца ужасно А смотри мы же с
not the first time we've met. I
тобой не первый раз встречаемся Вот я
think we'll meet in a couple of
думаю Встретимся через пару-тройку
months and
месяцев и
discuss the oil crisis.
по обсудим обсудим нефтяной кризис
good crisis. good interesting. But for now we
хорошо кризис хорошо интересно А пока
can talk about something else. You
можно о чём-то другом поговорить так Вы
yourself put it down to predict. And what to
же сами ложили по прогнозировать А о чём
predict about military military
по прогнозировать военный военные
actions.  again look what if
действия так опять же смотрите что если
we start to predict something now
мы сейчас начнём что-то прогнозировать
you will say again Let's meet in 3 months
вы скажете снова Давай через 3 месяца
You will say again Let's
встретимся Вы скажете снова Давай через
meet in 3 months no no So
3 месяца Встретимся нет нет Так о чём о
what to talk about how How do you assess let's
чём поговорить как Как вы оцениваете
say What about the development of the
допустим О чём по развитие развитие
military situation So damn  development
военной ситуации Так блин развитие
Look you said before let's
Смотри ты перед этим сказал давай
development development you say Oh we
развитие развитие ты кажеш О мы это не
can't check this let's check clean
можем проверить давай проверим чисты Так
So now We will also talk here I am
что сейчас Мы тоже будем говорить вот я
now  I'll say look in 2 months Yes
сейчас скажу смотри через 2 месяца Да
Putin will attack a NATO country will get an
Путин нападёт на страну НАТО получит
unreal beating and by
нереальных звездюлей и до 4
May 4 some analytics are justified
мая какой-то аналитики обоснованны
you understand not just Well so
понимаешь не просто Ну так вот так
look again I'm telling you
смотри ещё раз говорю я тебе говорю
this let's do it let's do it
такое давай так давай мы сделаем таким
we'll meet in months Yes and  then let
мы встречаемся через месяца Да и тогда
's talk about that or my
поговорим о том или моя аналитика по
gasoline analytics went If yes let's do it this way if I
бензину пошла Если да давай так если я
understood you correctly you claim that
тебя правильно понял ты утверждаешь что
this means this
вот этот значит это
situation will provoke a fuel crisis
ситуация спровоцирует топливный кризис
yes the country will have problems with sowing and there
да в стране будут проблемы с посевной и
will be problems with conducting military
будут проблемы с ведением военных
operations because of this not me  I think that
действий из-за этого не я считаю так что
if Ukraine continues to
если Украина продолжит такую
shell
интенсивность обстрела
oil refineries in the
нефтеперерабатывающих заводов
European part of the Russian Federation and the Urals with such intensity as it
европейской части РФ и Урала так как она
is doing now, it will not decrease, at
делает сейчас не уменьшит по крайней
least, yes, then with the onset of the sowing
мере да то с наступлением посевной
campaign, your fuel deficit will begin to increase,
компании у вас начнётся увеличиваться
which will grow depending on
который перерастёт в зависимости от того
how intensively Ukraine knocks out your
насколько интенсивно Украина выбьет ваши
capacities  generating will develop into a
мощности генерирующие перерастёт в
real fuel deficit in that its
реальный дефицит топлива в том её
real shortage discrepancy between
реальную нехватку несоответствие
consumption and consumption and this
потребления ответст потреблению и это
will result in a real blow and  on economics
выльется в реальный удар и по экономике
including military various matters
в том числе и по военным разным делам а
but if without general words somehow more
вот если без общих слов как-то побольше
specifics Can I get from you Russia if
конкретики Можно от тебя России если
specifics without general
конкретика без общих
words what do you
слов что ты
want what will happen on May 4
хочешь что буде 4 травня
Putin in me was alone that before May 4
Путин в мене ведин было что до 4 травня
Putin went
Путин поехал
Hello Hello  Where are you from
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы откуда
or where do I live and where do I live and where do you
родом или где проживаю и родом и где
live I come from the city of Abakan you know
проживаете родом с города Абакан знаете
such
такой
Khakassia Yes Khakassia my father is from
Хакасия Да Хакасия у меня отец из
Khakassia he just comes
Хакасии родом просто
from Cool And so usually he also doesn't know
из Круто А так обычно тоже не знает
where I live in Warsaw And why did you go to
где проживаю в Варшаве А почему уехали в
Warsaw Well to Poland in general to study
Варшаву Ну в Польшу вообще на учёбу
I study here and you are a Russian
учусь тут а вы русская
Khakass mestiza And how did your parents end up in Khakassia
хакаская метиска А как попали в хакасию
m
м
mom mom your father is from Yakutia so which
мама мама свы отец с Якутии так то а кто
of them is Tatar Who is Russian dad Tatar
из них татарин Кто русский папа татарин
mom Russian mom Russian from Tuva And dad
мама русская мама русская с Тувы А папа
how did mom Russian end up in Tuva she they
а как мама русская в Тувы попала она они
moved  just there in tvo it's all somehow
переехали просто туда в тву вот как-то
complicated Yes, my mother was actually born in the
сложно Да мама вообще рождена была в
village  khokhol in Voronezh region
селе хохол в Воронежской области
Yes, it's just that my father is ethnic
Да просто у меня отец Хакас этнический
Khakass Khakass and my mother is
Хакас о а мама
Ukrainian Well, well, I
украинка Ну ну у меня в роду хакасов
don't have any Khakass in my family, and where are you from? Well, I'm from
нет вот а вы сами откуда Ну сам с
California now
Калифорнии сейчас
Wow, that's cool, I've been there in Khakass for a long time, I don't know
Ого классно давно там в Хакас я не знаю
how your father is a Tatar, yes A  Khakassians they are
как у вас отец татарин да А хакасы они
also very jealous of the fact that
ещё очень ревностно относятся к тому что
if they marry someone other than
если выходят замуж или женится не за
Khakassian, my grandfather had big claims against my
Хакас вот у меня дед большие претензии к
father because my father Khakassian married
отцу имел Потому что отец Хакас женился
my mother Ukrainian and I have big
на маме Украинке и ко мне большие
problems because I left Khakassian,
проблемы потому что я уехал из хакаси
for them it's just  that I left the land of my
Это для них вот просто что я землю
ancestors right Well,
предков покинул прям
Khakassians, yes, they are like that in fact, to
Ну хакасы да они такие на самом деле мне
be honest, I don’t like Khakassians as a people
если честно хакасы не нравятся как народ
because they are very aggressive Well, I
потому что они очень агрессивные Ну
lived 17 years in Khakassia, I saw Khakassians
прожи 17 лет в хакаси я видела хакасов
from the inside, their life, but this They are similar in some way
изнутри их жизнь но это Они схожи чем-то
to Tuvans, Tuvans are  head Levintsy
с тувинца тувинцы на голову левинцы
immediately if anything all In short they Yes yes
сразу если что всех Короче они Да да
of course in Tuva this is a normal topic but the
конечно в Туве это нормальная тема вот а
Khakassians but they are from  same thing only
хакасы но они из той же оперы только мне
it seems to me that they are a little calmer than
кажется что они немножко поспокойнее чем
Tuvans
тувинцы
Yes yes yes Well something like that well Khakas I don't
Да да да Ну что-то такое ну Хакас не
know I never had a relationship with them well
знаю у меня никогда с ними отношения не
like well that The thing is that
складывались ну как бы ну ту Дело в том
this is why I will tell you I will explain to you
что это же почему я скажу я тебе объясню
like Khakas I'll explain why they don't like uh,
я как Хакас Объясню почему не любят ээ
not Khakassians Yes, like you If you were
не хакасов Да вот ты Если бы ты была
at least half Khakassian Like me, you
наполовину хотя бы Хакас Как я да тебя
would be perceived as one of our own Yes, we
бы воспринимали за свою Да у нас у
Khakassians have such a thing, well, like dogo dogo -
хакасов есть такой ну как бы дого дого -
this is the code Khakassian You know, Khakassians are
это кодекс Хакас Ты знаешь Хакас - это
Turks
тюрки
Yeah,
Угу Да
and there is a concept that Russia came to
и есть понятие что вот Россия пришла на
these lands and Russians are strangers here and for example
эти земли и русские тут чужие и например
even my mother from Ukraine was sent to
даже мою маму из Украины её прислали в
Abakan to work as a nurse, she was not
Абакан работать медсестрой её не
accepted until she
воспринимали пока она не женилась на не
married her father Khakassia and even then my grandfather was
вышла замуж за папу Хакас и то дед был
very much against it  they didn't talk
очень против отсюда они не разговаривали
there for 14 years with their father after that only later,
там 14 лет с отцом после этого аж потом
when the grandfather was old, they started talking
уже когда дед старый был начали говорить
And because the mother from Khakass was already
И из-за того что мама с хакасов уже
married Yes, her  accepted society
замужем Да её приняло общество
eh Well and how would it be treated differently And
э Ну и как бы по-другому относится А
if not Khakass here we should How would
если не Хакас вот есть мы должны Как бы
I be at least half Khakass since on my father's side
я я хоть наполовину Хакас раз по отцу
Khakass I am considered a Khakass Yes we should not
Хакас Я считаюсь хакасов Да мы не должны
perceive non-Khakass in our Republic
у себя в Республике воспринимать не
that is we have a policy
хакасов то есть у нас есть политика
displacement from the republic of non-Khakassian
вытеснения из республики не Хакас
population because the Soviet Union there
населения потому что Советский Союз там
Stalin Lenin they brought us different
Сталин Ленин они нам навели разных
Khakassian elements and it turns out we
хакасского элемента и получается нас
have become a minority there now according to the
стало меньшинство там сейчас вот По
last census by the way I looked Yes
последней переписи Я кстати смотрел Да
already Khakassians are quite large uh
уже хакасов довольно крупная
percentage ratio and every
ээ процентное соотношение и с каждым
year everything is growing. So you left  you are not
годом всё растёт Вот вы уехали вы не
Khakass you left Yes, I am half
Хакас вы уехали Да вот я наполовину
Khakass Yes, I still think sooner
Хакас Да Я всё равно всё-таки думаю рано
or later I will return to my homeland Yes, and
или поздно Я вернусь на родину Да и
we will build an independent Khakassia maybe
будем строит независимую может хакасию
or something like that when we cleanse it of Russians
или как вот когда от русских очистим так
just like Sakha Sakha is theirs too They are the same
же как Саха Саха тоже у них Вот они тоже
Turks they are making a policy of ousting
тюрки они делают политику вытеснения ээ
foreign elements that were brought in
чужеродных элементов которые навели во
during the Soviet Union, that's how it is, yeah, well, I
время Советского Союза вот так угу ну я
noticed that actually  I was at home
заметила на самом деле я была дома в
this year I noticed how much more
этом году я заметила насколько Ну больше
Khakassians appeared Because when I
хакасов появилось Потому что когда я
was younger there I was 13-14 years old I did
была помладше там мне было лет 13-14 я
n't see so many of them And now when I
не видела их такое количество А сейчас
go out on the street there are a lot of Khakassians
Выходя на улице очень много хакасов
not Khakassians who
не хакасы
have gone away
поуехавшие
and there are fewer And there are people like you  Yes, they
и меньше И вот таких как ты Да им
become uncomfortable, you
становится некомфортно вы
leave Well, in fact, to be honest, it
уезжаете Ну на самом деле если честно
seems to me that Abakan is not such a city at all. The
мне кажется Абакан - это вообще такой
city of dreams, what to do, Abakan,
город не Город мечты что делать абака
huts, like from other republics. And what is left for us?
изб Как из других республик А нам что
Coffins. Well, the republic is beautiful, and the
гробы Ну так республика красивая да
nature is cool, everything is beautiful, but it is specifically
природа классная всё красиво но именно
for life, as  standard of living in Abakan
для жизни как уровень жизни в Абакане
is that so Why standard of living
это вообще так Почему уровень жизни
because Moscow takes all resources
потому что Москва забирает все ресурсы
from
из
Abakan Buryati yes
Абакана буряти да
the task is
задача
to restore
восстановить
the original as if leadership of the Khakass
исконные как бы руководство хакасского
people over this land Do you know that for the
народа над этой землёй Ты знаешь что для
Khakass the Earth is sacred yes of course yes
хакасов Земля - Это святая да конечно да
as in the Russian Empire as they
как в Российской империи как нас
called us  you know, no Khakassians, Yenisei
называли хакасов знаешь нет енисейские
Kirghizians,
киргизы
that's how they called the Kirghiz in the description,
Да вот так в эти в описании п называли
that is, to us  even
сески киргизы то есть нам даже
refused our
отказывали в нашем
self-designation Well yes 18 years ago I left
самоназвания Ну да 18 лет назад я уехал
for this That is I am now 43 at 25 I
в это То есть мне сейчас 43 в 25 я уехал
left Abakan Wow well well okay so yes
из Абакана Ого ну ну нормально так да А
But would you return to
вот вы бы вернулись в
Abakan no If not Correct Because
Абакан нет Если нет Правильно Потому что
Khakassia for the Khakassians well
Хакасия для хакасов ну
simply well  I don't see any life
просто ну я не вижу вообще жизни никакой
in Abakan at all But I
в Абакане Но от слова совсем Абакан мне
don't like Abakan as a city at all I lived there for 17
не импонирует как город Я прожила там 17
years and there was something there
лет и чтобы там было что-то такое что
where I could find some opportunity
где бы я нашла какую-то возможность там
for myself Well, no It's clearly not in Abakan
для себя Ну нет Это явно не в акане Ну
Well, look at the principle of the dog Yes, this is what
это смотри принцип дог Да это что не
Khakass should not find life in Khakass
Хакас не должен находить жизнь в Хакас
So have you noticed that even people here Maybe
Так ты замечала что даже люди вот Может
when you lived in returned to Akan maybe you
ты когда жила в вернулась в акан может
noticed How the Khakass somehow look
замечала Как хакасы как-то смотрят коса
at you with a scythe like in a store you
на тебя вроде как в магазине ты
ask Yes to you  they answer something but
спрашиваешь Да тебе что-то отвечают но
somehow well not With respect No I haven't noticed
как-то ну не С уважением Нет не замечала
anything like that just notice
такого вот заметь
look it's not about me anymore if I
посмотри не про для меня больше если там
live there then It's probably already in more  at that
жить то Это наверно уже в более таком
age I don't know there are older ones But definitely
возрасте не знаю там постарше Но точно
not for young people because there is nothing for young people
не для моло потому что молодёжи нечего
to do in Abakan from the word at all that
ловить в Абакане от слова совсем что
maybe by the way Well by the way I don't know if you are watching
може кстати Ну я кстати не знаю ли ты
the news Well do you watch the news of Khakassia
новости Ну ты новости Хакасии смотришь
or not no no last year
или уже нет нет не вот в прошлом году у
I had Odnoklassnik  Sanya Prokhorov is a
меня был Одноклассник Саня Прохоров
gold medalist, a gold medalist, and we
золотой медалист золотой медалист и мы с
sat at the same desk. I was so-so, I was a
ним сидели за одной партой я так себе я
four-year student, but he was a five-year student,
на четвёрке учился да он реально пять у
that was consistent. Yes, he then went
него это было стабильно Да он пошёл
to work at a school, he taught
потом работать в школе преподавал
mathematics, and last year I may have
математику и в прошлом году может
heard that in Abakan it was very brutal.
слышала в Абакане было очень зверское
murder
убийство
by Wagner returned not not with an axe with an axe
вагнером вернулся не не топором топором
this is something else it turns out
это другое он получается вот
this is my classmate Sanya Prokhorov
этого моего одноклассника Саню Прохорова
he in short at this
он короче у этого
Wagnerites he is a math teacher
вагнеровцах он учитель математики
gave
поставил двойку
this student a two because he didn't learn
этому ученику потому что он не выучил
There Teremu something There Or that one came
Там терему что-то Там Или тот пришёл
dad In short to say that you have two  I'm
батя Короче сказать что у тебя два я
like you're the son of a special operation participant, you're
типа ты сын участника спецоперации тебе
like, they give you a two, you went to
типа что-то два ставят пошёл в это в
school for this  disassembly Yes, he started to talk like that
школу на разборке Да начал рать типа что
I, in short, this I, like, gave my life for you,
я короче этот я типа за вас жизнь
everything in general, in short, e head Sani
отдавал всё в общем короче э бошку сани
Prokhorov Yes, he, I don’t know, he had some kind of
прохорову Да он не знаю какой-то у него
knuckle duster there or something, what was it Yes, right
там кастет или что что это было Да прям
in the teacher’s room, in short, him
в учительское было короче его
and Sanya died in  ambulance ambulance
и Саня погиб в скорую скорая ещё
arrived they were taking this guy to intensive care on the way and he
приехала везли по дороге в реанимацию и
died they put him in jail like well How they
умер этого чувака посадили как бы ну Как
convicted him and he signed a contract with Mino
осудили и он Подписал контракт с Мино
Bron returned to the front That is he is just a
Брон вернулся на фронт То есть он просто
math teacher Sanya Prokhor Russian
учителя математики Саню Прохор русский
guy Russian guy you know Here Yeah and
парень русский парень знаешь Вот Угу а
this is Wagner Khakas
это да Вагнер Хакас
and  everything and he just just he yes he was still
и всё и он просто просто он да он ещё
there on the driver yelled at him when he was beating
там на ехавший орал на него когда бил
like just some kind of
типа просто какой-то
wildness it was then on the noise you can it you
дич это тогда на шумела ты может это ты
can well you don't watch the news yeah haga
может ну не смотришь новости да хага
then it would
тогда это так
be like that my relatives would also
бы у меня родственники тоже там мне
throw money at me there  look, like, wow,
скидывали там вот смотри типа ничего
there was a video there, kids were filming it at
себе там видео прямо было дети снимали в
school, like, well, on the video, how he
школе типа ну на видео как он его
beats him up, you, Kostya, there's an order there,
избивает ти вот Косте там орди
No, he's A  also this is this he knows yet How are
Да нет он А ещё это это зна он ещё л Как
you Russian like this well Agnets Khakas
вы русский типа вот этот ну Агнец Хакас
some kind of was no This is terrible but this one
какой-то был нет Это ужас а вот этот
with an axe that was What was Vines
топором то который был Это что винес был
no and with an axe Yes with an axe Tvinnitsa this is
нет а с топором Да топором Т винниц это
damn and there now it's tough too  there was yes
блин да и там сейчас жёстко тоже было да
there was another Wagner vets Yes
там ещё было ещё один Вагнер вец Да
onl
онл
grandma watched this news
бабушку смотрел эти новости
grandma 83
бабушка 83
years old she was half paralyzed
года она была наполовину парализована у
her hands did not work She
неё руки не работали Она под
was under the care of social services oh
обеспечением социальных служб была ой
Hang out with him
Зависай
roulette could not stand our
сним рулетка не выдержала наших
stories subscribe to mi Telegram right
историй подпишись на ми Telegram прям
now axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through srg or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okm video also tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we will oblige you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
to maintain constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you about This
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про Цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe N
подпишись N